<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<questionaires>
    <questionaire name="phq-9">
        <title>Patient Health Questionaire (PHQ-9)</title>
        <acronym>PHQ-9</acronym>
        <table>
            <primary_question>Over the past 2 weeks, how often have you been bothered by any of the following problems</primary_question>
            <column>Not at all</column>
            <column>Several days</column>
            <column>More than half the days</column>
            <column>Nearly every day</column>
            <question>Little interest or pleasure in doing things</question>
            <question>Feeling down, depressed, or hopeless</question>
            <question>Trouble falling asleep, staying asleep, or sleeping too much</question>
            <question>Feeling tired or having little energy</question>
            <question>Poor appetite or overeating</question>
            <question>Feeling bad about yourself - or that you are a failure - or have let yourself or your family down</question>
            <question>Trouble concentrating on things such as reading the newspaper or watching television</question>
            <question>Moving or speaking so slowly that other people could have noticed. Or, the opposite - being so
                fidgety or restless that you have been moving around a lot more than usual</question>
            <question>Thought that you would be better off dead or of hurting yourself in some way</question>
        </table>
    </questionaire>
    <questionaire name = "Mood Disorder Questionaire">
        <title>Mood disorder questionaire (PHQ-9)</title>
        <acronym>MDQ</acronym>
        <table>
            <primary_question>Has there ever been a period of time when you were not your usual self and...</primary_question>
            <column>Yes</column>
            <column>No</column>
            <question>you felt so good or so hyper that other people thought you were not your normal self or that you were so hyper
                that you got into trouble?</question>
            <question>you were so irritable that you shouted at people or started fights or arguments?</question>
            <question>you felt much more self-confident than usual?</question>
            <question>you got much less sleep than usual and found that you didn't really miss it?</question>
            <question>you were more talkative or spoke much faster than usual?</question>
            <question>thoughts raced through your head or you couldn't slow your mind down?</question>
            <question>you were so easily distracted by things around you that you had trouble concentrating or staying on
                track?</question>
            <question>you had more energy than usual?</question>
            <question>you were much more active or did many more things than usual?</question>
            <question>you were much more social or outgoing than usual, for example you telephoned friends in
                the middle of the night?</question>
            <question>you were much more interested in sex than usual?</question>
            <question>you did things that were unusual for you or that other people might have thought were excessive,
                foolish or risky?</question>
            <question>spending money got you or your family in trouble?</question>
        </table>
    </questionaire>
</questionaires>
